http://www.dukehealth.org/privacy/website-privacy-policy

Skip Navigation
Close Banner
COVID-19 (Coronavirus) Update
Read about the safety precautions in place throughout Duke Health to keep you safe. Please note visitor restrictions are in place.
Notice of Privacy Practices
The policy below applies to all Duke University Health System websites, including, but not limited to:
dukehealth.org
corporate.dukehealth.org
physicians.dukehealth.org
dukemychart.org
Duke is committed to protecting your online privacy. In general, you can visit Duke websites without revealing any personal information. However, you may be asked to provide personal information to gain access to some of our content and services. This information helps us to better ascertain and address the health care needs and concerns of site visitors.
All personally identifiable data that you enter on this site is not sold or given to any third parties.
Analytics Tools
We use analytics tools and other third party technologies, such as Google Analytics (including Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting and Remarketing with Google Analytics) and DoubleClick Cookies, to collect non-personal information regarding you in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our online Sites and/or Services. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, geo-location, demographic and interest data, and other similar information.
The third party analytics companies who collect information on our Sites and/or Services and other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.
In addition to our use of technologies as described herein, we may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to you based on your use of Duke Health Sites and/or Services and to otherwise collect and use data about your use of Duke Health Sites and/or Services.
You may opt out of the Google advertising cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page. Google has additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, and Restrictions.
Optimization
We use user information, including behavioral metrics, and other non-personally identifiable information to operate, provide, improve, and maintain our Sites and Services, to develop new products and services, to prevent abuse and fraud, to personalize and display advertisements and other content for you, and for other administrative and internal business purposes.
Email Communications
Communication that you send to us via the email links and forms on our site may be shared with a customer service representative, employee, or medical expert that is most able to address your inquiry. We make every effort to respond in a timely fashion once communications are received.
Because email does not provide a completely secure and confidential means of communication, please do not use e-mail if you wish to keep your communication private, instead, call 888-275-3853 with your request.
Minor’s Privacy
The websites are intended for a general audience and not directed to children less than 13 years of age. Some portions of the websites, however, may be intended as appropriate for a mixed audience of users under and over 13 years of age, or for users under 13 years of age (e.g., Minor (12-17) MyChart Accounts).
As a non-profit organization, Duke University Health System’s collection of children’s personal information is not governed by the U.S. Children’s Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). We do not intend to collect personal information as defined by COPPA (“Children’s Personal Information”) from minors under the age of 13 without parental consent. For example, Minor (12-17) MyChart Accounts are available to Minors aged 12-17 subject to parental consent. For more information, FAQs.
Any California residents under the age of eighteen (18) who have registered to use the websites, and who posted content or information on the websites, can request removal may contact us, detailing where the content or information is posted and attesting that you posted it.  We will then make reasonable good faith efforts to remove the post from prospective public view or anonymize it so the minor cannot be individually identified to the extent required by applicable law. This removal process cannot ensure complete or comprehensive removal. For instance, third-parties may have republished or archived content by search engines and others that we do not control.
Complaint Process
If you have a complaint or problem, or if you believe your privacy rights have been violated, you may contact us. Please indicate the reason for contacting us. Our customer service department will forward your complaint to the appropriate Duke University Health System department for response or resolution.
Last Updated: August 13, 2018
Back To Top
